

Technical Skills and Competences

Substantial Technical Literacy

Affinity towards modules and systems optimisation

Decent Software Products and Systems Knowledge

Operating Systems, Graphic interfaces, Microsoft Office

Multimedia processing

Content Management Systems

WordPress: DBMS

Hardware Components

Constructive modules, computer peripherals

Local Area Networks

✓ Building, configuring, optimisation and support of Local Computer Networks, posts, clients and servers

Social Skills & Competences

Building, managing and motivating teams devoted to marketing research and new products introduction

Acquired in Condor
Commerce Ltd. and Condor
Design Ltd, Sofia 1994-1996
during the years of my
Higher Education

VELIN **SKENDEROV**

JOB APPLICANT

Profile

A qualified steady individual with strong interpersonal entrepreneurial skills, prone to bring the appropriate face to the business by delivering first-class customer service. Could offer creative thinking outside of the box, within a team or individually, to the utmost satisfaction of relevant stakeholders, in line with the market realities and competitive strategy followed by to mutual benefit of all parties concerned. Being well experienced in retail and information technologies sectors, I consider myself as properly suited to provide outstanding customer support as a part of first-rate Housing Construction process.

Experience

2014 - 2020

Business Management Systems Ltd, Customer Relationships Department

Customer Support Specialist, Bourgas.

Description of the job position and esponsibilities

2012 - 2013

Infrastructure Technology Services and Engineering Ltd, Information Technologies Administration, Quality Support Department

Receiving Orders Technologist, Bourgas. Description of the job, position and responsibilities.

2011 - 2012

LUKOIL Technology Services Bulgaria Ltd, Information Technologies Administration, Organisational Support Group

Receiving Orders Leading Technologist, Bourgas.

Description of the job, position and responsibilities.

2008 - 2011

LUKOIL Technology Services Bulgaria Ltd, Information Technologies Administration, Information Technologies Organisational Support Group

Specialist/Information Technologies Operational Support , Bourgas.

Description of the job, position and responsibilities.

Organisational Skills and Competences

Marketing

✓ Sales of goods (mass products) and services

Introduction to the market

Services, Information
 Products and Technologies induction

General

Interdisciplinary interests

✓ general knowledge;

Shotokan Katate and Judo practice

Driving License

Category B

Disposable Referent Documents

Letter of Recommendation

✓ from Business Management
Systems Ltd Managing
Director (last employer)

Business English Certificate

✓ Cambridge C1 Business
 Higher
 Business Benchmark
 Advanced C1
 Cambridge Business English
 Vantage B2

Document Doctoral Course

✓ Bulgarian Academy of Science, Central Laboratory of Biomedical Engineering

Certificate

 Design and Programming Support of Distributed Control System MIC

Master's Level Qualification Degree Certificate

University of National and World Economy, Sofia

2005 - 2008 LUKOIL Technology Services Bulgaria Ltd, Information Technologies Administration, Program Technologies and Databases Department

Programmer, Bourgas.Description of the job, position and responsibilities.

2002 - 2005

LUKOIL Neftochim Burgas JSC,
Information Computing Center, Cash
Accounts Balance Department

Programmer, Bourgas.

Description of the job, position and responsibilities.

2001 - 2002 KRS Iliya Iliev Sole Proprietorship Company, Yambol

Trade, import and distribution of radio-electronic equipment, black & white household appliances, mobile communication, Bourgas.
Customer Support Specialist

Description of the job, position and responsibilities

Education

2009 - 2010

Business English

Foreign Languages and Management

Centre, Bourgas

Cambridge English: Business Certificate

Cambridge English: Business Certificates (BEC) C1 Business Higher

2008 - 2009 Business English

Foreign Languages and Management Centre, Bourgas Cambridge English: Business Certificates (BEC) B2 Business Vantage Certificate

2007 - 2008 Business English

Foreign Languages and Management Centre, Bourgas Cambridge English: Business Certificates Vantage

2007 - 2007 Intuitional Fuzzy Sets - Theory and Application

Bulgarian Academy of Science, BME, Sofia Doctoral Course "Theory and Application of Intuitional Fuzzy Sets"

2001 - 2001 Design and Software Support of Disributed System MIC

MICONT Ltd, Sofia
Design and Software Support of Distributed
System MIC for Control of Technological
Plants in Real Time

Higher Education Diploma

University of National and World Economy, Sofia

Secondary Education Diploma

✓ High School of Natural Sciences and Mathematics "Academician Nikola Obreshkov", Bourgas

Certificate of acquired professional qualification Programmer of Computer Equipment

 ✓ High School of Natural Sciences and Mathematics "Academician Nikola Obreshkov", Bourgas 1989 - 1999

Higher Education

University of National and World Economy, Sofia Industrial Management Master

1984 - 1989

Secondary Education

High School of Natural Sciences and Mathematics "Academician Nikola Obreshkov", Bourgas Information Computing Machines Operator/Programmer Certificate

Foreign Languages

Russian

Reading Writing Speaking



English

Reading Writing Speaking



Contact

- ★ Bourgas
- **** +359 56 996693 / 889 687481
- **1** +359 888 470027
- ✓ Velin.Skenderoff@gmail.com